chods-cheats.com 2016-06-25

# CVM Software Solutions Ltd.

CVM Software Solutions Ltd. ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your
privacy.
This policy (together with our terms of use http://www.chods-cheats.com/termsofuse.pdf and
any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect
from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following
carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will
treat it. We keep certain basic information when you visit our website and recognise the
importance of keeping that information secure and letting you know what we will do with it.
For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is CVM
Software Solutions Ltd. of Office 35, Burley Hill Trading Estate, Leeds, LS4 2PU
(registration number 8316858).
This policy only applies to our site. If you leave our site via a link or otherwise, you will be
subject to the policy of that website provider. We have no control over that policy or the
terms of the website and you should check their policy before continuing to access the site.
INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU
We may collect and process the following data about you:
         Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.chods-cheats.com
          (our site). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our
          site, subscribing to our service or requesting further services. We may also ask you
          for information when you report a problem with our site.
         If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
         We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although
          you do not have to respond to them.
         Details of your visits to our site and usage of other downloadable material including,
          but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs, operating system, browser
          usage and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing
          purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.
IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES
We may collect information about your computer, including but not limited to (where
available) your IP address, operating system, and browser type, for system administration and
to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users'
browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual and we will not collect
personal information in this way.
We may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is
stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to
                                                  1
www.chods-cheats.com Privacy Policy

your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more
personalised service. They enable us:
        To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
        To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site
         according to your individual interests.
        To speed up your searches.
        To recognise you when you return to our site.
You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you
to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to
access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will
refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.
MALICIOUS PROGRAMS
Use of any downloaded materials may result in your computer’s memory being searched for
malicious programs. This includes but is not limited to debuggers, packet manipulation
software, cracking software, reverse engineering software. Detection of any software deemed
malicious may result in the immediate termination of your account without review.
WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside
the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the
EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other
things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision
of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or
processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated
securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions
will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which
enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password
confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure.
Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security
of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have
received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent
unauthorised access.
USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION
                                                 2
www.chods-cheats.com Privacy Policy

We use information held about you in the following ways:
        To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you
         and for your computer.
        To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or
         which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such
         purposes.
        To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and
         us.
        To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to
         do so.
        To notify you about changes to our service.
We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you
with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they
may contact you about these by [post or telephone].
If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties
for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect
your data.
DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION
We may disclose your personal information to third parties:
        In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose
         your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
        If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with
         any legal obligation, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information
         with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and
         credit risk reduction.
YOUR RIGHTS
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We
will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such
purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes.
You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the
forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting
us at info@jamvo.co.uk.
Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner
networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note
                                                3
www.chods-cheats.com Privacy Policy

that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any
responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any
personal data to these websites.
ACCESS TO INFORMATION
The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be
exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to
meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and,
where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. However, we advise that you check this page
regularly to keep up to date with any necessary changes.
CONTACT
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be
addressed to info@jamvo.co.uk.
                                                  4
www.chods-cheats.com Privacy Policy
